<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://sofyk.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://sofyk.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-09-11T15:01:41-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sofy Kabachek</title><subtitle>Welcome to my site!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Lunch - Game</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/02-29-2016-lunchgame/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lunch - Game" /><published>2016-02-29T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2016-02-29T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/lunchgame</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/02-29-2016-lunchgame/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sofyk.itch.io/lunch/&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/fullsize/lunch.png&quot; alt=&quot;corporate espionage&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An interactive fiction game that lets you stroll through the conversation a couple is having at a restaurant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Play it &lt;a href=&quot;https://sofyk.itch.io/lunch/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lunch is a game about a couple that is having an argument that is entirely unrelated to the actual issues troubling the relationship. It is about two people reading into things, yet never stating their mind. At least not during that lunch. It will be up to the player to figure out what actually troubles the relationship.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="games" /><summary type="html">An interactive fiction game that lets you stroll through the conversation a couple is having at a restaurant.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://sofyk.com/pictures/fullsize/lunch.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://sofyk.com/pictures/fullsize/lunch.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 08/10/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/08-09-2015-scotch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 08/10/15" /><published>2015-08-09T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-08-09T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/scotch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/08-09-2015-scotch/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Murder Scene: The murder occurred in a park, at night. Apparent suicide with a small gun. A well known detective. The victim’s house has been broken into and searched.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sarah put a hand on her mouth, and shut her eyes tight. She was well aware that it won’t help her be more quite. But somehow, on a strange level, it helped her feel invisible as a large shadowy character tore through her grandfather’s apartment. It was a small two bedroom apartment on the third floor. Sarah hid in the closet of the guest bedroom. It seemed to have been visited by the intruder already, and she hoped that he would not come back for a second look through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sarah visited her grandfather every Thursday night. She stopped by after work, and they shared a glass scotch. She also, inevitably, got to hear some stories about the good old days at the precinct. She heard the one about his partner getting shot in the rear at least ten times before. She would have loved to be hearing it again tonight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When she got to grandpa’s place this time, the door was unlocked and cracked open. No signs of tampering with the lock. Someone had a key. She opened the door slowly, and found the living room in turmoil. All the drawers were pulled out and flipped. She stopped and listened. The place seemed empty, so she advanced; slowly and silently. She almost reached the master bedroom when she heard the stranger. He tore one of the drawers from the nightstand, and emptied its contents onto the bed. She froze. No sudden movements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holding her breadth, light as a feather, she snuck into the guest bedroom and into the closet. There was a small safe in there. Grandpa made sure to disable the sound on the number pad. She was convinced that an occasion like this was the reason. Inside was a small revolver. The bullets were in a different safe, in the master bedroom. She hoped she wouldn’t need them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She made sure not to move the sliding closet doors. He might be observant. She didn’t want to give him any reason to double check this room. A few breadths. A few counts. The shadowy character seemed to remain focused on the master bedroom, and Sarah felt secure enough to send a preconfigured SOS message from her smart watch. The message was setup to send her coordinates and a phrase “call 911.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The text was received by two phones. One belonged to Richard, a private investigator and Sarah’s colleague. The other belonged to grandpa. It didn’t ring in the apartment. In fact in didn’t ring at all. It was smashed by the weight of the owner when he fell of a park bench. It was currently being inspected by two officers that found it and the owner next to a small hand gun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Murder Scene: The murder occurred in a park, at night. Apparent suicide with a small gun. A well known detective. The victim's house has been broken into and searched.Sarah put a hand on her mouth, and shut her eyes tight. She was well aware that it won’t help her be more quite. But somehow, on a strange level, it helped her feel invisible as a large shadowy character tore through her grandfather’s apartment. It was a small two bedroom apartment on the third floor. Sarah hid in the closet of the guest bedroom. It seemed to have been visited by the intruder already, and she hoped that he would not come back for a second look through.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 08/03/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/08-02-2015-dangerous-spills/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 08/03/15" /><published>2015-08-02T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-08-02T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/dangerous-spills</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/08-02-2015-dangerous-spills/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Romance: The relationship begins when two people that frequent the same cafe for lunch accidentally spill coffee on each other. One of the characters is currently in a relationship. Love has no secrets. One of the characters was adopted at a young age.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Oh, no! I’m such a mass. I’m so sorry…” Nora was vigorously rubbing the chest of a stranger with her sleeve, trying desperately to make the fresh stain of coffee disappear.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“It’s alright…” the stranger tried to comfort her.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nora disregarded this attempt. “I can get it dry cleaned. There’s a place right around the corner, I can take it there now! Wait…no…you might need your a shirt now…do you need this shirt now?” She asked, her sleeve still struggling to soak the stain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Stranger grabbed her hand, and held it tightly in his. “Really. It’s alright.” This seemed to have been the only way to stop the rubbing. “I have a spare in my office. This truly is not the end of the world, miss.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Um…Nora. You can call me Nora.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nora. What a pleasure. You can relax now. Trust me, this shirt has weathered a lot worse.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ha, well, at least it’s not red wine…I spilled red wine on my blouse last week. Might as well throw it out! I mean, I haven’t yet…hoping for a miracle, I guess…I’m babbling. Am I babbling? I feel like I’m babbling…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Try shaving cream.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s what I use to remove tough stains.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Really…?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Works surprisingly well.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ll do that…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stranger smiled, shook Nora’s hand, and turned to walk away. For some strange reason, at that exact moment, Nora was overcome with the feeling that she might not see this stranger ever again. And that somehow if he does disappear entirely, it will make her life a little less interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Who should I blame if it ruins my blouse?” She called after him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ha?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The shaving cream, if it doesn’t…look, it’s just my clever way of asking for your name.” She smiled nervously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He smiled in answer. “It’s Charles.” He shook her hand again. “I actually come here all the time. You just never noticed me before, because I am usually proficient at avoiding dangerous spills.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, yeah? What made you suck so bad at it today?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I just had to meet you.” His expression altered slightly, and his lips bore a more serious curve. “At last.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a weird thing for a stranger to say to another stranger, thought Nora, as she nervously swallowed and wriggled her hand from his.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Don’t worry, Nora. Your first intuition was right. Your life will indeed become a little more interesting now.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Romance: The relationship begins when two people that frequent the same cafe for lunch accidentally spill coffee on each other. One of the characters is currently in a relationship. Love has no secrets. One of the characters was adopted at a young age.“Oh, no! I’m such a mass. I’m so sorry…” Nora was vigorously rubbing the chest of a stranger with her sleeve, trying desperately to make the fresh stain of coffee disappear.“It’s alright...” the stranger tried to comfort her.Nora disregarded this attempt. “I can get it dry cleaned. There’s a place right around the corner, I can take it there now! Wait...no...you might need your a shirt now...do you need this shirt now?” She asked, her sleeve still struggling to soak the stain.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/30/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-29-2015-bloot/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/30/15" /><published>2015-07-29T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-29T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/bloot</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-29-2015-bloot/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SciFi/Space: You are within a densely populated city on a colonized planet. The reason for the ship’s / colony’s existence has been hidden from its occupants. Your character has trouble adjusting to their new life. World War Three resulted in one globally unified government.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Move to Pluto, they said. It’s the hip place for young professionals, they said. Well it doesn’t look like anyone is really interested in this young professional.” Nick pointed two thumbs at himself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This gesture didn’t seem to amuse the administrative assistant with whom he was sharing his woes. “I’m sorry, Mr. Frankford. But the other candidate was simply better qualified for this position. But we will gladly keep your resume on file, should any more appropriate positions open up in the future.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“You do that, Ms. Botinelly. You do that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Is there anything else I can help you with, Mr. Frankford?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nick considered responding with a joke about needing help with money and/or food. But after examining the harsh look on the young assistant’s face he decided his wit and charm would be better applied to a more worthy cause. “No, Ms. Botinelly, I believe you’ve done everything your company would be willing to do for me.” He sighed and turned to walk away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Good day, Mr. Frankford.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see about that…” he muttered to himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cold wind struck Nick as he walked out the building. He popped the collar on his cheap suit to shield himself from the cold and the disapproving stares of the crowded street. This was supposed to be much easier. His education and experience was supposed to be sufficient. Now he’ll have to ask his roommate for another loan for the rent. Patrick can afford it of course. He didn’t make the mistake of studying to be a theoretical physicist. He was a programmer at Bloot; improving the performance of interplanetary teleportation. Unfortunately they weren’t looking for a theoretical physicist. They already had one. A Nobel prize winning one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should have stayed on Mars, he told himself once again. And once again he reprimanded himself for falling for those damn hipster commercials calling for the smart youth to join the new Pluto colonies. What a load of bullshit. It wasn’t the commercials though that brought him here. He wasn’t willing to admit that yet, but as with many of his rash decisions, this was the result of an infatuation. And all his friends were moving here anyway…as he let his thoughts drift back to the going away party they all had on Mars, a strange sensation yanked him back to reality. Someone was watching him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">SciFi/Space: You are within a densely populated city on a colonized planet. The reason for the ship's / colony's existence has been hidden from its occupants. Your character has trouble adjusting to their new life. World War Three resulted in one globally unified government.“Move to Pluto, they said. It’s the hip place for young professionals, they said. Well it doesn’t look like anyone is really interested in this young professional.” Nick pointed two thumbs at himself.This gesture didn’t seem to amuse the administrative assistant with whom he was sharing his woes. “I’m sorry, Mr. Frankford. But the other candidate was simply better qualified for this position. But we will gladly keep your resume on file, should any more appropriate positions open up in the future.”“You do that, Ms. Botinelly. You do that.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/29/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-28-2015-largs-and-norb/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/29/15" /><published>2015-07-28T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-28T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/largs-and-norb</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-28-2015-largs-and-norb/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fantasy/Magic: You are in an abandoned city. You are a bounty hunter. Precognitive abilities allow you to turn deadly events into useful situations. You must find rare magical ingredients for a cure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Two orcs leaned against a gate at the entrance to an old city. The dark night was lit only by a few camp fires tucked behind the walls of the city. No doubt belonging to the friends and companions of the fine two gentleman, Largs and Norb, currently leaned against the gate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“He always asks me about my future plans, you know?” Offered Largs, hoping to entertain his companion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Who?” Norb asked, appearing to be caught off guard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Who asks you about future plans?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The general…he’s like, what do you want to do in two year? What do you want to do in five years? Like anyone knows. I wanna be alive, that’s what I want.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Is that what you told him?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No, are you kidding?! I told him I want to be a sergeant.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ha! What did he say?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Asked me how I plan to achieve that. How am I supposed to know?! I’m just a soldier, I do what I’m told!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, with this type of thinking you’ll never move up in life. You need to show some initiative.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Shut up! What initiative did you show?!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I organized a cherry picking troop every other weekday to supplement our nutritional intake. It will definitely reflect on my mid year performance review.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I feel like I should decapitate you just on principle for that. I mean, how on earth is that helping us become the great invincible army?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Proper nutrition is very important.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As if!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m serious. When’s the last time you ate a salad?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t need salad! I’m a damn orc! My proper nutrition consists of fresh human flesh.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well, that certainly explains your figure.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Largs scoffed at the offending remark. But before he could rebuke the improper evaluation of his physique, Largs noticed Norb’s head role past him. What a shame, he thought, I really did enjoy those cherries. It was his last thought before his head joined Norb’s in a leisurely roll down the hill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eldor, the dark assassin, tucked an escaped strand of hair behind a pointed elven ear. Although his task didn’t explicitly call for an assassination, it was evident by the location of operation that his particular skills will be essential. Eldor was tasked with the extraction of two humans taken hostage by the army of orcs and goblins presently occupying the ruins of the city Iscelldor. The most important of which was Ellenor, a rogue wizard for hire who was in possession of herbs essential for curing the elven queen. The other, Roger, a bounty hunter that was in the process of delivering Ellenor to the nearest human precinct when they were ambushed, was dispensable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Fantasy/Magic: You are in an abandoned city. You are a bounty hunter. Precognitive abilities allow you to turn deadly events into useful situations. You must find rare magical ingredients for a cure.Two orcs leaned against a gate at the entrance to an old city. The dark night was lit only by a few camp fires tucked behind the walls of the city. No doubt belonging to the friends and companions of the fine two gentleman, Largs and Norb, currently leaned against the gate.“He always asks me about my future plans, you know?” Offered Largs, hoping to entertain his companion.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/28/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-27-2015-film-cassette/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/28/15" /><published>2015-07-27T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-27T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/film-cassette</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-27-2015-film-cassette/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Action/Thriller: You are in a hotel room. You have an important photograph in your pocket. You are being followed throughout the story. You must deliver sensitive information.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I looked through the curtain. It was as dark outside as it was in this small hotel room. The damn heat took out the power in the entire block. Sweat rolled down my brow. I told myself it was the heat, but a persistent voice in the back of my head urged me to get my shit together. I’m supposed to be a professional. At least that’s what the sign I glued to my door said. A certified private investigator. The fact the my certificate was for HVAC repair and maintenance was just a small omission I had to propagate in order to get this first gig. Besides I only had a few weeks left on that online Criminal Justice degree. I’m practically an expert by now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I noticed some movement around the corner of the street. It was a couple. Laughing. No care in the world. What a nice existence. Honestly, I have no idea why I thought this would be a good career plan. I guess HVAC technician didn’t have the spark I was looking for, and mystery writer didn’t pan out as well as I hoped. This seemed like the next best thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The film cassette was burning a hole in my jacket pocket. Metaphorically speaking. I was acutely aware of it pressing against my ribs. I thought it was a clever idea to shoot the photos on film. No trace, no copies, no cloud. I had full control, and the only copy. I even set-up a little developing lab in my office. The problem was, I sucked at developing photos. I burnt through a whole pack of photograph paper trying to get some nice print of that film. Quite literally. I had to get rid of the bad copies somehow. Metal trash can and some Bio-Lite did the trick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knew that the wife wouldn’t be the only interested in some pictures of a senator’s off hours. No, it’s not what you think, not what she thought either. It’s much worse. And now I’m smack in the middle of it all. With my only evidence rolled up in a little tube.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A knock on the door snapped me back into reality. Shit. I wasn’t really expecting anybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Action/Thriller: You are in a hotel room. You have an important photograph in your pocket. You are being followed throughout the story. You must deliver sensitive information.I looked through the curtain. It was as dark outside as it was in this small hotel room. The damn heat took out the power in the entire block. Sweat rolled down my brow. I told myself it was the heat, but a persistent voice in the back of my head urged me to get my shit together. I’m supposed to be a professional. At least that’s what the sign I glued to my door said. A certified private investigator. The fact the my certificate was for HVAC repair and maintenance was just a small omission I had to propagate in order to get this first gig. Besides I only had a few weeks left on that online Criminal Justice degree. I’m practically an expert by now.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/27/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-26-2015-aorp/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/27/15" /><published>2015-07-26T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-26T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/aorp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-26-2015-aorp/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SciFi/Space: You are on a deep-space rescue mission. Your character becomes trapped within a simulated consciousness without realizing it. Your character is an influential government figure with access to almost everything. Humans in the future are genetically modified to be perfect.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Madam President? President Krishna? Ma’am…?” The voices vaguely registered in her subconscious. It was the last things she heard from the physical world. Her mind began constructing an alternate reality almost immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a protection mechanism implemented on a basic genetic level. Developed in the late 2200’s, it was design to preserve the the brain’s capacity when the body sustained great trauma. With the presumption that the rapier of the trauma would be so long, that the acclimation to an ordered reality would be too drastic when the patient awoke again, if an alternate ordered reality was not maintained in it’s place. This solution provided the safe reacclimation of many patients, and was generally regarded as a great success. It would have been the case with President Krishna as well, if she was not the first president to utilize the Telepathic Control Room technology in her presidential office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TCR technology has been around for ages. Even longer than the Alternate Ordered Reality Protocol. But as with most governmental updates, it took a very long time to permeate into the White House. It was designed to be foolproof. Even in the event of AORP triggering. In fact, it was design to disengage and transfer to the acting veep as soon as the president entered AORP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet it did not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richard Nuremberg, chief architect on the White House TCR project, currently attempting to maintain the president’s hold on the physical reality using the rudimentary method of calling her name, was beginning to suspect sabotage. It would take him some time to audibly admit that though, since it directly indicated the existence of a major flaw in his architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Madam President, please…stay with me…” Richard whispered desperately, as it dawned on him that she was fully engaged in her AORP while maintaining full control of WH-TCR; capable of engaging any of the White House systems with the power of thoughts and recollection. Including, and certainly not limited to, the controls of Space Force One which they all currently occupied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We have to shut down the White House TCR immediately!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">SciFi/Space: You are on a deep-space rescue mission. Your character becomes trapped within a simulated consciousness without realizing it. Your character is an influential government figure with access to almost everything. Humans in the future are genetically modified to be perfect.“Madam President? President Krishna? Ma’am…?” The voices vaguely registered in her subconscious. It was the last things she heard from the physical world. Her mind began constructing an alternate reality almost immediately.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/16/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-15-2015-the-sleep/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/16/15" /><published>2015-07-15T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-15T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/the-sleep</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-15-2015-the-sleep/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Horror/suspense: The climax occurs at a cottage where a character seeks refuge. An old superstition is uncovered and put to the test. An investigative journalist . The lights begin to flicker.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This was a terrible idea. Robert knew that long before he found himself in the attic of this abandoned cottage. Yet following terrible ideas to terrible places has been part of Robert’s job description as a journalist for quite a while now. He always felt that the purity of his pursuit for uncovering and shedding light on the truth has attracted the attention of a great unexplainable force; always protecting and guiding him. But tonight he feared that even that force did not dare to enter this place with him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The local town has been hit with a strange affliction. people fall into a deep sleep. not really a comma, because they keep chanting in strange language in their sleep. the whole town has been quarantined. and a special high level quarantine area was established for the patient. only relief and rescue professionals, and parents of minors within the quarantine were allowed to enter the town. after some legal fights, and a court ruling, a handful of journalists were allowed to enter as well. Robert was one of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one is allowed to leave.all the patients were afflicted simultaneously after a short power fluctuation in the town. both the CDC and the John Hopkins department of infectious disease cannot identify the pattern of infection.
Robert found that all patients have had personal items stolen. Not all were of significant monetary value, but they all were of great personal importance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the train of thefts leads him to the cottage. There in the attic he finds the thief afflicted by the sleep, drooling and mumbling. He was passed out in the middle of a strange design drawn with chalk, surrounded with the stolen items. on a podium next to him was an old book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Robert photographs the scene. Trying to capture every detail. And leaves the place as fast as possible. something about quiets even his curiosity. He sends the pictures to a friend of his, a theology professor at Princeton, in hopes that he might know someone that could shed light on this strange scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Horror/suspense: The climax occurs at a cottage where a character seeks refuge. An old superstition is uncovered and put to the test. An investigative journalist . The lights begin to flicker.This was a terrible idea. Robert knew that long before he found himself in the attic of this abandoned cottage. Yet following terrible ideas to terrible places has been part of Robert’s job description as a journalist for quite a while now. He always felt that the purity of his pursuit for uncovering and shedding light on the truth has attracted the attention of a great unexplainable force; always protecting and guiding him. But tonight he feared that even that force did not dare to enter this place with him.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/14/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-13-2015-sarah-and-eric/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/14/15" /><published>2015-07-13T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-13T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/sarah-and-eric</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-13-2015-sarah-and-eric/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Romance: An introduction made by a close friend sets up a romantic relationship. One of the characters is afraid of making a commitment. Opposites attract. The characters bond while going to a place that holds sentimental value.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They both showed up to cheer-up Robbie after a rough breakup. Even though they were best friends with Robbie for years now, they’ve never met. Robbie was convinced that the universe would implode if they ever do. They’ve heard stories of each other though. Many stories. None of them seemed to convince the other of the necessity for an introduction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this was an emergency. Robbie was on the verge of buying a ticket to Tonga. He aimed to follow his now-ex girlfriend who was recently engaged to a local rugby player. Robbie was convinced that if only they could see each other again, their love would reignite into a fiery sun, and all will be well. Sarah and Eric knew better. They arrived at the scene just in time to stop Robbie from confirming his flight order.
Of course Robbie would claim that he was nowhere near confirming the flight, simply entertaining an idea. And that slamming his laptop shut and throwing it across the room may have been an over reaction. But, as was mentioned before, Sarah and Eric knew better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Eric, meet Sarah. Sarah, that’s Eric.” Robbie said with slight hesitation. He would be a little more concerned about his laptop, if his world was not in the process of imploding.
“Pleasure.” Sarah smiled, as was proper, and gave Eric a sturdy handshake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’ll see about that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever one has to make difficult and complex decisions with a wide array of consequences, it is highly recommended to have two great friends that will invariably take the opposite side and present thorough justification that theirs is the preferable choice. It’s not entirely as simple as a devil and angel on one’s shoulder; morality is such a vague concept in daily life decisions. But more like the good side of two oppositely charged coins. Now they were shaking hands. And on this historic occasion, Eric and Sarah agreed; Robbie should not be going to Tonga.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Romance: An introduction made by a close friend sets up a romantic relationship. One of the characters is afraid of making a commitment. Opposites attract. The characters bond while going to a place that holds sentimental value.They both showed up to cheer-up Robbie after a rough breakup. Even though they were best friends with Robbie for years now, they’ve never met. Robbie was convinced that the universe would implode if they ever do. They’ve heard stories of each other though. Many stories. None of them seemed to convince the other of the necessity for an introduction.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Warm-up Sketchbook 07/13/15</title><link href="http://sofyk.com/07-12-2015-zorn/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Warm-up Sketchbook 07/13/15" /><published>2015-07-12T17:00:01-07:00</published><updated>2015-07-12T17:00:01-07:00</updated><id>http://sofyk.com/zorn</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://sofyk.com/07-12-2015-zorn/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fantasy/Magic: You are living in an evil and corrupt city. Your character is reclusive and has no status in society. You have two pet dragons. You must unite humanity under one leader to face a larger threat.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Zorn was petting a red scaled beast resting on his lap. I could almost swear he was purring. The dragon, that is. A second dragon was curled up next to his feet. This might have seemed charming if the two pets were not fire breathing devils, owned by an antisocial magus who was only ever seen in public twice. Both times are generally regarded as not the most pleasant visits. Although that was before the new party arrived. The definition of pleasant has since shifted. Not for the better, might I add.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He lifted his finger to signal me to come closer. Hesitantly I made my way to the steel chair at the head of the table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Well.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t a question. In fact I wasn’t sure what that was supposed to mean. Probably that I should leave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“well…” I hesitated. “Look, I know you don’t care. And that’s fine. It’s been fine for years now. We don’t really want that to change. I can’t even imagine what it would be like if you actually cared. Oh gods, that would be a complete disaster-”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Get to the point.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Right…I…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“NOW!” The two dragons lifted their heads, the purring stopped, and they slowly shifted their focus to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We need you, Zorn. You’re the only one who can get a hold of the capitals.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That is inaccurate.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But it is! Everyone else has been taken, or worse, converted by the party. Gosh darn it, if I had the spells I’d do myself…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You can have the spells.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You would do that?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t want any part in this. I don’t care for your silly politics.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This has gone far beyond politics. There is something very wrong going on here. I mean, they closed ‘Pots and Bat Wings’ and no one can figure out where Ruth disappeared to. And the pub around the corner, you know the one, lava something…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Lava Pit.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Right! They found out that a bunch of us were getting together there…and…and…Zorn, we’re desperate.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You had your secret political movement in the Lava Pit?! It was the only place clear of all that filth, and you brought it there?!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We didn’t have secret meetings! It was the only place where we could have a drink without getting snitched on by some party youth. And now it’s gone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You should not have brought this to the Lava Pit. You right wing scum!”
“So you’re not gonna help us.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zorn lowered his gaze, and returned to petting the dragon in his lap. He seemed to have disappeared again into his own world, like he always does. This was a long shot anyway. They all told me so. I guess I’m just too naive. I mean what do you expect from a loner who spends most of his time with fire breathing reptiles. With a sigh I turned to walk away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Is Saffron all right?” A low tone torn from a distant place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We…we don’t know. We can’t find her either.” My voice broke. “And she had nothing to do with any of it…”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I will help you find her.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a warm-up sketch. Find out more &lt;a href=&quot;/sketchbook-intro/&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sofy Kabachek</name></author><category term="writing-sketchbook" /><summary type="html">Fantasy/Magic: You are living in an evil and corrupt city. Your character is reclusive and has no status in society. You have two pet dragons. You must unite humanity under one leader to face a larger threat.Zorn was petting a red scaled beast resting on his lap. I could almost swear he was purring. The dragon, that is. A second dragon was curled up next to his feet. This might have seemed charming if the two pets were not fire breathing devils, owned by an antisocial magus who was only ever seen in public twice. Both times are generally regarded as not the most pleasant visits. Although that was before the new party arrived. The definition of pleasant has since shifted. Not for the better, might I add.</summary></entry></feed>